Isaac Carnes

Full Stack Developer

Pittsburgh, PA 15206

Email: IsaacJDeveloper@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /Isaac-J-Carnes Github: /IsaacJCarnes

Portfolio: isaacjcarnes.github.io/ij-portfolio/

Imaginative Full Stack Developer interested in creating a fun user experience with responsive design and effective compact code. Holds a certification in Full Stack Web Development. Driven code designer focussed on creative design and efficiency when developing.

Technical Skills

Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, C# Technologies: SQL, NoSQL, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Express, React, Node, Handlebars, jQuery, Bootstrap Core Concepts: Leadership, Time-Management, Communication, Reliable, Avid Learner,

Relevant Experience

Psychology Student Researcher, Apr 2017–Feb 2019 Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, PA Work with a contracted developer and post-graduate students to develop a simple python game to relate decision making to motion tracking in the test subject.

Additional Experience

Technology Associate, Aug 2021–Jan 2022 Staples, Pittsburgh, PA

Shipment Coordinator, Jan 2021–Jul 2021 VSMPO Tirus, Pittsburgh, PA

Projects

Card Graphix | github.com/wl0194/card-graphix | card-graphix.herokuapp.com

- A heroku web app built with react that allows the user to create, customize and export their own business card.
- Responsible for team management, some page design, card creation functionality
- Heroku, React, Apollo JS, Cloudinary, Html2Canvas, js2pdf

Dog Endorsement Website | github.com/lsaacJCarnes/DogEndorsementWebsite | dog-endorsement-website.herokuapp.com

- A heroku web app built with node handlebars that allows the user to find local adoptable dogs using the petfinder api.
- Responsible for team management, page design, backend linking and API implementation
- Heroku, MySql2, Handlebars, Petfinder API

Maze Game | github.com/lsaacJCarnes/MazeGen | isaacjcarnes.github.io/MazeGen

- A github pages web app that allows the user to play through a simple maze and save their times into their local storage.
- Responsible for team management and maze creation system
- Github Pages, Giphy API

Education

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development: University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA